Topical files 1
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Topical files 1, 2.1.9.4
  - Tyrolean singers, circa 1937; 19 (Box 1616)
    - [Tyrolean singers: Group of men in costumes singing, one playing an instrument], 1
    - [Tyrolean singers: Group of men playing instruments], 2
    - [Tyrolean singers: Line of men in costumes doing high-kicks], 3
    - [Tyrolean singers: Group of men in costumes singing, one playing an instrument], 4
  - United States Olympic Committee, 1960 - 1961; 20 (Box 1616)
    - [United States Olympic Committee: Lowell Thomas in front of tubes], 1
    - [United States Olympic Committee: Lowell Thomas in front of tubes], 2
    - [United States Olympic Committee: Lowell Thomas in front type of equipment], 3
    - [United States Olympic Committee: Lowell Thomas in front type of equipment], 4
  - United States Ski Team [color photograph], 1971; 21 (Box 1616)
    - The 1971 U.S. Alpine Ski Team; To: Mr. Lowell Thomas; Happy Birthday! 4/6/71, 1
  - U. S. Steel, 1960 - 1961; 22 (Box 1616)
    - [U.S. Steel: Lowell Thomas standing outside of a nursery looking at a nurse holding a baby to the window], 1
    - [U.S. Steel: Lowell Thomas standing outside of a nursery looking at a nurse holding a baby to the window], 2
    - [U.S. Steel: Lowell Thomas standing outside of a nursery looking at a nurse holding a baby to the window], 3
    - [U.S. Steel: Lowell Thomas standing outside of a nursery looking at a nurse holding a baby to the window], 4
    - [U.S. Steel: Lowell Thomas standing outside of a nursery looking at a nurse holding a baby to the window], 5
    - [U.S. Steel: Lowell Thomas standing outside of a nursery looking at a nurse holding a baby to the window], 6
  - Unusual, 1973 - 1977; 23 (Box 1616)
    - [Unusual: Portrait of a woman]Gray [address], 1
    - Verso: Gray [address], 1-verso
    - [Unusual: Two women, one sitting on steps], 2
  - Venezuela: The New Look, circa 1954; 24 (Box 1616)
    - Airview of Caracas, capital city of Venezuela, with a population of over 1,000,000, 1
    - Verso: Airview of Caracas, capital city of Venezuela, with a population of over 1,000,000, 1-verso
    - President of Venezuela-General Marcos Perez Jimenez, 2
    - Verso: President of Venezuela-General Marcos Perez Jimenez, 2-verso
    - Airview of the 30-story Centro Bolivar towers, in the heart of downtown Caracas., 3
    - Verso: Airview of the 30-story Centro Bolivar towers, in the heart of downtown Caracas., 3-verso
    - Hotel Tamanaco in Caracas, Venezuela., 4
    - Verso: Hotel Tamanaco in Caracas, Venezuela., 4-verso
    - Night shot of the Olympic Stadium at University City., 5
    - Verso: Night shot of the Olympic Stadium at University City., 5-verso
    - August 1954-Demolition work begins to clear path for new thruway in Caracas. December 1954, 6
    - The Autopista-superhighway between Caracas and the seport of La Guaira., 7
    - Verso: The Autopista-superhighway between Caracas and the seport of La Guaira., 7-verso
    - Not an airview of the new New York State Thruway--but, the Pan American Highway as it enters Caracas, 8
    - Verso: Not an airview of the new New York State Thruway--but, the Pan American Highway as it enters Caracas, 8-verso
    - Panoramic view of the Universitiy City in Caracas., 9
    - Verso: Panoramic view of the Universitiy City in Caracas., 9-verso
    - Happy kindergarten children sing songs during a play period, 10
    - Verso: Happy kindergarten children sing songs during a play period, 10-verso
    - Airview of Lake Maracaibo oil fields, 11
    - Verso: Airview of Lake Maracaibo oil fields, 11-verso
    - Ore train at Cerro Bolivar iron mine., 12
    - Verso: Ore train at Cerro Bolivar iron mine., 12-verso
    - The world's largest earthen dam. Costing $50,000,000, the new Guarico Dam, 13
    - Verso: The world's largest earthen dam. Costing $50,000,000, the new Guarico Dam, 13-verso
    - Farm colony at Turen, Venezuela., 14
    - Verso: Farm colony at Turen, Venezuela., 14-verso
    - Juan Griego Harbor, Island of Margarita., 15
    - Verso: Juan Griego Harbor, Island of Margarita., 15-verso
    - The incorporation of the working people in the extensive cultural development taking place in the country is best illustrated, 16
    - Verso: The incorporation of the working people in the extensive cultural development taking place in the country is best illustrated, 16-verso
    - Dominating the "Avenue of the Heroes" are these two 100 foot towers..., 17
    - Verso: Dominating the "Avenue of the Heroes" are these two 100 foot towers..., 17-verso
    - Airview of new low-cost housing project, 2nd of December, in Caracas, Venezuela., 18
    - Verso: Airview of new low-cost housing project, 2nd of December, in Caracas, Venezuela., 18-verso
    - Modern highways such as these in eastern Caracas have helped free the city of traffic congestion., 19
    - Verso: Modern highways such as these in eastern Caracas have helped free the city of traffic congestion., 19-verso
    - The "Avenue of Heroes" pays tribute to Venezuela's national heroes, 20
    - Verso: The "Avenue of Heroes" pays tribute to Venezuela's national heroes, 20-verso
    - Angel Falls-world's highest..3,212 feet., 21
    - Verso: Angel Falls-world's highest..3,212 feet., 21-verso
    - Cable railway to top of 7,000 foot Mount Avila., 22
    - Verso: Cable railway to top of 7,000 foot Mount Avila., 22-verso
    - Ski lodge on top of 15,380 ft. Mirror Peak in Venezuelan Andes, 23
    - Verso: Ski lodge on top of 15,380 ft. Mirror Peak in Venezuelan Andes, 23-verso
  - Paula von Hellens [includes color photograph], 1966 - 1971; 25 (Box 1616)
    - [Paula von Hellens: Girl standing with hand on her hip]To Uncle Lowell Thomas From Krista & Arno in December 1970, 1
    - [Paula von Hellens: Girl standing with hand on her hip], 2
    - [Paula von Hellens: Girl standing with hand on her hip], 3
    - [Paula von Hellens: Girl standing with hand on her hip], 4
    - To Uncle Lowell Thomas From Krista & Arno in December 1970, 5
    - Verso: To Uncle Lowell Thomas From Krista & Arno in December 1970, 5-verso
  - V - miscellaneous [color photograph], 1976 - 1981 September 22; 26 (Box 1616)
    - [no description], 1
  - Thomas J. Watson, Jr., 1980; 27 (Box 1616)
    - [Front of christmas card from Thomas J. Watson, Jr. and family to Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [Inside of christmas card] The wedding of Susan Watson and Stephen Whitman; May 31, 1980; May 31st was a wonderful day for us, too! Olive & Tom Watson, Jr., 2
    - [Front of christmas card from Thomas J. Watson, Jr. and family to Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [Inside of christmas card], 4
    - [Back fo christmas card] With all best wishes for a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year; Olive and Thomas Watson, Jr., 5
  - Westinghouse 1943 war effort, 1943 January 5 - February; 28 (Box 1616)
    - [Westingtonhouse 1943 war effort: Man at podium, speaking], 1
    - [Westingtonhouse 1943 war effort: Group of people and officers], 2
    - [Westingtonhouse 1943 war effort: Lowell Thomas among a crowd of people asking for his autograph], 3
    - [Westingtonhouse 1943 war effort: Lowell Thomas among a crowd of people asking for his autograph], 4
    - [Westingtonhouse 1943 war effort: Lowell Thomas on top of an army tank], 5
    - [Westingtonhouse 1943 war effort: Man wearing a helmet on an army vehicle], 6
    - [Westingtonhouse 1943 war effort: Crowd of soldiers sitting behind Lowell Thomas, who is speaking at the podium], 7
    - [Westingtonhouse 1943 war effort: American flag and Army/Navy flag], 8
  - Noel and Ada Wien, undated; 29 (Box 1616)
    - Season's Greetings; Noel and Ada Wien, 1
    - Verso: This picture on our wedding anniversary-only the 38th, 1-verso
    - Note: Mr. and Mrs. Noel Wien [address], 2
  - Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland), 1968; 30 (Box 1616)
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 1
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 2
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 3
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 4
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 5
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 6
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 7
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 8
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 9
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 10
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 11
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 12
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 13
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 14
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 15
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 16
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 17
    - [Photographs for Wisconsin Project (Matt Keland): Portrait of man], 18
  - W - miscellaneous [the White Cottage], 1940; 31 (Box 1616)
    - [W - miscellaneous [the White Cottage]: House], 1
    - [W - miscellaneous [the White Cottage]: View of snowy land and snowcapped mountains], 2
    - Mt. Elmore; Taken from living room-front view, 3
    - Verso: Mt. Elmore; Taken from living room-front view, 3-verso
    - [W - miscellaneous [the White Cottage]: Snowy land], 4
    - [W - miscellaneous [the White Cottage]: House], 5
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 3] The White Cottage; Mansfield Road; Stowe, VT. Aug 27-1940; Mr. Lowell Thomas. Radio City; N.Y.; Dear Mr. Thomas-To be sure, I am one of your radio fans, 6
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 3], 7
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of 3], 8
  - W - miscellaneous [color photograph], circa 1970s; 32 (Box 1616)
    - [W-miscellaneous [color photo]: Group picture outside of house (Family photo?)], 1